{
    "id": "c7388665ffbd4167aa145c62aedbe716",
    "title": "Active and Passive Voice Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She will not recognize us. / We ………………………… by her.",
            "description": "In the simple future tense we make the passive forms by putting the past participle form of the verb after will be.",
            "answers": [
                "will not recognize",
                "will not being recognized",
                "will not be recognized"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "15f52c9e46694299b0a133139a96ccf4"
        },
        {
            "question": "They didn’t invite me, but I went anyway. / I ………………………… but I went anyway.",
            "description": "In the simple past tense we make the passive form by putting was / were before the past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "wasn't invited",
                "wasn't being invited",
                "wasn't inviting"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "daabe72e1d6d46429dc70fc2697769d4"
        },
        {
            "question": "They broke up the table for firewood. / The table ………………………. up for firewood.",
            "description": "\r\nIn the simple past tense we make the passive form by putting was / were before the past participle form of the verb.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "broke",
                "had broken",
                "was broken"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6da06a367a5d41c0913dc04d218fc8a9"
        },
        {
            "question": "This book will change your life. / Your life ……………………….. by this book.",
            "description": "In the simple future tense we make the passive forms by putting the past participle form of the verb after will be.",
            "answers": [
                "will be changing",
                "will be changed",
                "will have been changed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9437fb8ee9c7498cbfd8b5517f9d4c26"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has won the first prize. / First prize …………………………. by her.",
            "description": "\r\nIn the present perfect tense, we make the passive form by putting the past participle form of the verb after has/have + been.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "has won",
                "has been won",
                "had been won"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "39653cdf6f7d46499df2683f19c0118b"
        },
        {
            "question": "A friend of mine is repairing the car. / The car ……………………………. by a friend of mine.",
            "description": "In the present continuous tense we make the passive form by putting is/am/are + being before the past participle form of the verb. ",
            "answers": [
                "is repairing",
                "is repaired",
                "is being repaired"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a503ef276ea24c8a8145057a5493d111"
        },
        {
            "question": "The immigration officer questioned us. / We …………………………. by the immigration officer.",
            "description": "\r\nIn the simple past tense, we make the passive form by putting was/were before the past participle form of the verb.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "were questioning",
                "were questioned",
                "were being questioned"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cba05c5268744b17918393b3cfc05898"
        },
        {
            "question": "They speak English in Nagaland. / English ……………………… in Nagaland.",
            "description": "\r\nIn the simple present tense, we make the passive form by putting is/am/are before the past participle form of the verb.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "is speaking",
                "is spoken",
                "is being spoken"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ff88f655d62343b1977b7678a8460a9d"
        },
        {
            "question": "His attitude shocked me. / I ……………………… by his attitude.",
            "description": "\r\nIn the simple past tense, we make the passive form by putting was/were before the past participle form of the verb.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "had shocked",
                "had been shocked",
                "was shocked"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "acb22cb519bf41b4a9a4caa9c4eeb9a6"
        },
        {
            "question": "She had already sent the parcel. / The parcel ……………………………. by her.",
            "description": "In the past perfect tense, we make the passive form by putting the past participle form of the verb after had been. ",
            "answers": [
                "has already been sent",
                "had already been spent",
                "was already spent"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c1a4b90b96dc4db8854149c2529adace"
        },
        {
            "question": "They will hire some people to do the job. / Some people ………………………… to do the job.",
            "description": "In the simple future tense, we make passive forms by putting the past participle form of the verb after will be.",
            "answers": [
                "will be hiring",
                "will have hired",
                "will be hired"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "40c411160a1a4e56bec85abfd29a7329"
        },
        {
            "question": "Her silence worries me. / I ……………………….. her silence.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am worrying about",
                "am worried about",
                "have worried about"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b2e214187c8141ba8e1f5dc693396705"
        }
    ]
}